A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Office and Home Files FA1353
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects and Properties, 1923-2009; 3; 76.78 Cubic Feet 177 containers
  - New York and Pocantico, 1923-2009; 3_5
    - Greenrock Corporation - Billing Analysis, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Board Meetings, 1988-2005 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Employee Manual, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Financials - Audit/Budget, 1989; 1998-2005 (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Future Ownership, 1992-2005 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Gatehouse Expansion, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Heavy Equipment Storage, 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Historic Hudson Valley Lease, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Greenrock Corporation - National Trust Lease Option, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Greenrock Corporation - New Building - Part 1-2, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
    - Greenrock Corporation - New Building - Cost Sharing / LSR Contribution, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Recapitalization, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Contract, 1992-2004 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Shareholders' Agreement, 1987-2004 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Snyder, Robert W. D. - 563 Bedford Road (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Greenrock Corporation: Snyder, Robert W. D. - Sleepy Hollow Cemetery Plots (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Snyder, Robert W. D., 1986-1995 (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Special Projects - General, 1990-2004 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Special Projects - Complete and Ongoing, 1998-2005 (Box 11, Folder 8-17)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Staff, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Staff - Transfer to 5600 Payroll (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Staff Housing - Appraisals - 503 Bedford Road (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Staff Housing - Appraisals - 517 Bedford Road (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Staff Housing - Appraisals - 100 Lake Road (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Staff Housing - Appraisals - 102 Lake Road (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Staff Housing - Appraisals - 108 Lake Road (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Staff Housing - Closing Report, Sale to David Rockefeller, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Cambridge Associates Study, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Endowment Study, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Hudson Highlands Proposal, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Pocantico Historic Area, 1986-1992 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Public Charity Status, 1986-1991 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - Union Church Lease, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Hudson River Research Institute, 2000-2003 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Hudson Valley Project - General, 1966-2000 (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
    - Hudson Valley Project - River Access, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Kiernan, Frances (Brooke Astor Book), 2002 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - 308 Hudson Street - General, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - 308 Hudson Street - Appraisal, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - 308 Hudson Street - Closing Documents, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - 308 Hudson Street - Klein, Stephanie - Notes, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - 308 Hudson Street - Sale of Property - General, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - 222 Riverside Drive, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      Closing documents on sale of LSR's penthouse apartment, October 1, 1993.
    - Naval Institute Press - Albert Murray Biography, 1996-1997 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - New York Community Trust, 1988-1990 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Optima Fund - Partnership Agreement, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - PBS - The American Experience - Rockefeller Family Special, 1998-2000 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Pocantico - First Refusal Rights, 1988-1993 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Pocantico - Historic Area Plans - General, 1983-1996 (Box 40, Folder 7-9)
    - Pocantico - Historic Area Plans - Coach Barn Tangibles, 1989-1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Pocantico - Historic Area Plans - Kykuit and Coach Barn Tangibles, 1994-1999 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Pocantico - Historic Area Plans - Visitation, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Pocantico - Historic Area Plans - Future Inside Park, 1979-1999 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico - Rockwood Hall - IBM - General, 1997-2003 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Pocantico - Rockwood Hall - LSR-IBM Agreement, 1998 September 24 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Pocantico - Rockwood Hall - IBM - Revised Restrictions, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Pocantico - Playhouse Future, 1998-2002 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Pocantico - Kykuit Reproductions, 1993-1995 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Pocantico - LSR Rights of Ownership (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Pocantico - David Rockefeller - Farm Barns Project, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Pocantico - Shared Expenses, 1988-2003 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - General, 1992-1994 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - A-11 - General (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - A-11 - Closing Documents (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Article 78 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - B3 - Gift to Lucy (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - B3 - Conservation Easement, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - B3 and B4 - Appraisal, 1996-1998 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - B5 - Sale to Lucy, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - B5 - Appraisal, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - B26 - Zegarelli (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - 569 Bedford Road, 1994-1995 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Breuer House, 1999-2001 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Lake Road Subdivision Parcels, 2000-2003 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - LSR Property Planning - General, 1966-1988 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - LSR Property Planning - General, 1989-2000 (Box 45, Folder 2-3)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - LSR Property Planning - B4 and B5 Study (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Sisters of Mercy - Marymount - General, 1972-2004 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Sisters of Mercy - Marymount - Appraisal, 1989-2003 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Sisters of Mercy - Marymount: Austin Corp. Properties - General, 1998-1999 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Sisters of Mercy - Marymount: Austin Corp. Properties - Letter Agreement, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Sisters of Mercy - Marymount - Schulman Realty Group - Contract and Closing Documents, 1998-1999 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Phelps Memorial Hospital - Giving, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Village Green, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Rockwood Hall - Doyle, 1977-2000 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Rockwood Hall - Leases, 1981-1996 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Rockwood Hall - General, 1974-1996 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Rockwood Hall - General, 1980-1996 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Rockwood Hall - History, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Rockwood Hall - Site Studies - Sasaki Associates, 1983-1984 (Box 406, Folder 1)
    - Rockwood Hall - Appraisals, 1985 (Box 406, Folder 2-3)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Route 9 Bridge, 1996-1997 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Sasaki Report on Tree Planting, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Southern Acres - General, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Southern Acres - Austin Corporate Properties, 1997-1998 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Pocantico - LSR Properties - Toll Brothers, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Pocantico - Water System - General, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Pocantico - Water System - Improvements, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Pocantico - Village Green - Sale to NAR Jr., 2003-2006 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Powers of Attorney, 1989-2000 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Preston Perry Design - LSR Conference Room, 1997-1998 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      Structure Tone, Plans, Proposals, Schedules
    - Preston Perry Design - LSR Office Renovations, 1997-1998 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Reader's Digest, 1991-1996 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Reader's Digest - Wallace Funds, 1985-1998 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Reader's Digest - Wallace Funds - Fund for Hudson Highlands, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Recovery Institute - Advisory Board, 1997-2001 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Recovery Institute - General, 1997-2000 (Box 52, Folder 1-2)
    - Recovery Institute - Financials, 1997-1999 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Recovery Institute - Fundraising, 1997-2000 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Recovery Institute - Hart Survey, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Recovery Institute - "Ardent Spirits" - Script, 1997-1998 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Recovery Institute - "Ardent Spirits" - WNET, 1997-1998 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Recovery Institute - "The Road to Recovery" - A Landmark National Study on Social Attitudes toward Alcoholism, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Republican Main Street Partnership, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, Barbara ("Bobo") - Loan, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Fixed Fee Analysis, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller and Company - General, 1990-2008 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Power of Attorney, 2006 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Financial Services - General, 1970-1999 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Analysis by Harper Woodward, September 1976. Memo regarding a meeting with Drs. Thomas, Good, and Cotzias; Joint Services and Personal Office, 1966-1975. Meeting of Board of Managers, December 16, 1970 and other materials.
    - Rockefeller Group Inc. / Rockefeller Center Properties (RGI/RCP) - General, 1981-1995 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Larry - Promissory Note - Office Recapitalization, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Larry - Financial projections for Wyatt and Ryan Rockefeller, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Biography by Cary Reich, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller University - General, 1998-2003 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Ross School, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Roussel, Christine - Art of Rockefeller Center, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      LSR helped fund the publication
    - Union Church - New Parking Lot, 1993-1995 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Union Church - General, 1989-2004 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - General, 1995-2004 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - Appraisals, 1994-2002 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - C-11, 2002-2008 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - Easements, 1989-2004 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - Hackley School - General, 1997-2002 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - Hackley School - Closing Documents, 1998-2002 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - Kent House, 2000-2004 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - Outer Lodge, 1982-1993 (Box 55, Folder 10-11)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - Rockwood Hall - General, 1997-1999 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - Rockwood Hall - Appraisals - A5 and A25, 1996-1998 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - Rockwood Hall - Phelps Hospital - General, 1997-2001 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - Rockwood Hall - Phelps Hospital - Title Report, 1996-2002 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Rockwood Hall - News Clippings Scrapbook, 1969-1974 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - Sale to Mark and Nelson Rockefeller - General, 1992-1997 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - Sale to Mark and Nelson Rockefeller - Contracts, 1993-1995 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - Sleepy Hollow Water Tower, 2004-2005 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - LSR Properties - Pocantico - B3 - B4 - B5 - General, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - General Correspondence, 1993-2006 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - General, 2004-2005 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - B23 - Appraisal - Village Green, 2005-2007 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - C8 - Appraisal - LSR Woodlands, 2005 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - C11 - Appraisal - 9 acres, 2005 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D7 and D17 - Appraisal - East and South Lawns, 2005-2006 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D10 - MOU - Sale to Nelson and Mark, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D10 - Kent House - Sale to Nelson and Mark, 2005-2007 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D10 - Kent House - Subdivision, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D10 - Appraisal - Kent House, Stephen House, Cottage, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico: D10 - Appraisal on .83 acres (County House Road), 2005-2006 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico: D10 - Appraisal (Stephens House on 8.5 acres), 2004-2005 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D10 - Sale - Kent House - Term Sheet, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico: D10 - Appraisal on 22.388 acres, 2004 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D10 - Appraisal on 8.2 acres, 2005 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D11 - General - Kykuit Guest House, 2005 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D11 - Appraisal - Kykuit Guest House, 2004-2005 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D19 - Appraisal Park Entrance - 50 percent ownership, 2004-2005 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D19 and D20 - Notice of Deed to National Trust, 2008 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D20 - Appraisal 50 percent ownership - Sisters Road, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D21 - Appraisal County House Road - 50 percent ownership, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D22 - Appraisal - Greenrock Corporation, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Pocantico - D22 - Appraisal - Greenrock Corporation - Sale to David Rockefeller, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico Land Sales, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Friends and Associates Trust - Corporate Documents, 1988-2004 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Financial Services - Recapitalization, 1992; 2004 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Financial Services - Office Loan Guaranty, 2002-2004 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Financial Services - McDonald Loan Guarantee, 2001-2006 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Financial Services - Subleases, 1993-2007 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller Financial Services - Unfunded Liabilities, 1987-1991 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller Financial Services - Office Space, 2008 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Waletzky, Lucy - General, 1989-2006 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - General, 1999-2006 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Family Cemetery Corporation - Miscellaneous, 1989-2003 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - LSR Fund - Art Gifts, 1995-2006 (Box 101, Folder 7)
      Miscellaneous gifts.
    - LSR Fund - Rockwood Hall - Gift to State and MSKCC - General, 1998-1999 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - LSR Fund - Rockwood Hall - Gift to State - Deed of Gift and Closing Documents (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - LSR Fund - Rockwood Hall - Transfer to LSR Fund, 1998 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - LSR Art - Miscellaneous, 1997-2001 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - LSR - Trusteeships, 1989-1997 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - LSR - Public Relations - General, 2000-2002 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - LSR - Public Relations - Interviews, 1992-1997 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - LSR - Public Relations - New LSR Biography, 2000 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - LSR - Political Giving, 1982-1998 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Hudson River Valley Commission - Summary Report, 1966 February 1; pamphlet (Box 103, Folder 3)
      LSR was Chairman of the commission
    - Greenways in the Hudson River Valley, 1988; pamphlet (Box 103, Folder 4)
      Introduction by LSR. Published by Sleepy Hollow Press.
    - Book - Air World's Great Airports - Newark and Kennedy, 1978; 1981 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Book - Rickenbacker, 1923 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      Inscribed to Jean Mauze.
    - Book - Prayers from the Ark, bound volume (Box 105, Folder 3)
      By Carmen Bernos de Gasztold; translated by Rumer Godden. With gift letter to LSR from Whitney Bourne Atwood.
    - Pocantico Hills Properties - Land Use Study, 1989 February 27 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Pocantico Hills Properties - Rockwood Hall - Appraisal, 1990 March 13 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Rockwood Hall - LSR Fund - Closing, 1999 April 12 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Pocantico Property - Parcels C-16, C-34, and C-35 - LSR Fund, 1994-1995 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Rockefeller Family Office - Analysis, 1976 September (Box 116, Folder 9)
      Analysis of the Rockefeller Family Joint Office by Harper Woodward.
    - LSR Estate - LSR Photograph Collection - General, 2005 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - LSR Estate - Greenrock Allocations, 2005 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Pocantico - General, 1988-2006 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Pocantico - Historic Area Plans, 1997-2000 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico - Partition - Rights of Ownership, 1980s (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Westchester Properties, 1941-1983 (Box 126, Folder 1-4)
      Ownership documents.
    - LSR - Westchester Properties, 1941-1995 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Westchester Properties, 1941-1999 (Box 127, Folder 2-3)
    - LSR - Philipsburg Manor - Appraisal, 1969 (Box 130, Folder 5)
      Property.
    - LSR - Miscellaneous, 1973-2004 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - LSR Estate - Pocantico Property - D-23, Stafford Yard, 2001-2007 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - LSR Estate - Sale Results - Spreadsheet, 2005 October 31 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - LSR Estate - Room 5600 - Disposition of Items, 2005-2009 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - LSR Estate - Room 5600 - Office Space, 2007-2008 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Properties - Pocantico, A16, 2009 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - LSR Estate - LSR Offices - Furniture Disposition, 2008-2009 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - LSR Estate - Wyoming - Final Report and Settlement Documents, 2009 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - LSR Estate - Pocantico, Parcel A-16 - Sleepy Hollow Cemetery, 2004-2009 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Properties - Pocantico - A16, 2009 (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Union Church - Dedication of the Window of the Cherubim, 2000 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - General, 1997-2009 (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1988-2008 (Box 184, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller State Park Preserve, 1980-2005 (Box 184, Folder 14)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Carriage Collection - Deed of Gift, 1999-2000 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Sale to David Rockefeller, 2006 (Box 186, Folder 12)
    - Pocantico Land Use Study, 1981-1982 (Box 302, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Center - New York Hilton, 1961; 1963 (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - LSR - The Ross School/The Ross Institute, 1990s-2000 (Box 363, Folder 1-2)
    - LSR - The Ross School - Courtney Ross, 1993-2003 (Box 363, Folder 3-4)
    - LSR - Kykuit - Opening, 1994 May 14 (Box 367, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Manual for Tank and Basement Shelters, Pocantico Hills, NY and Woodstock, VT, 1965 January (Box 367, Folder 5)
    - LSR - A Report on the Forest Conditions of Property Administered by Greenrock Corporation, 1970 January 1 (Box 367, Folder 6)
  - Princeton, 1980-2004; 3_6
    - Princeton University - Assorted Articles, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Princeton University - 5 Million Dollar Gift of Land, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Princeton University - Forrestal Campus, 2000-2001 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Princeton University - General, 1993-1998 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Princeton University - Center for Human Values - General, 1990-2004 (Box 50, Folder 5-6)
    - Princeton University - Center for Human Values - Annual Reports, 1990-2003 (Box 50, Folder 7, Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Princeton University - Moyers' Panel - "Mind, Faith, and Spirit", 1998-1999 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Princeton University - University Chair for Philosophy and Human Values, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Princeton University - Woodrow Wilson Award - LSR, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate and Investments, 1942-2009; 3_7
    - LSR - Property Acquisitions, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - LSR Estate - Crestone Property - Appraisal, 2001-2006 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Intervivos Trust (1999) - Wade Martin House Sale, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Intervivos Trust (1999) - Crestone Property - General, 1999-2004 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Investment File Guide, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Marx, Frank: Note, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Maui Property - General, 1988-1998 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Maui Property - Kipahulu Point Park Project, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Meetings - 5600 - LSR Current Activities, 1993 May 21 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - 1934 Trust - Loan Program (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - 1934 Trust - 2002 Income Request (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - 1934 Trust - Termination Provisions (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - 1934 Trust - Invasion Requests (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - 1934 Trust - General, 1985-2006 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - 1997 Associates Trust - General, 1997-2004 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - 1997 Associates Trust - First International Oil (see Louis Marx - Investments) - Stock Gift (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - 1997 Associates Trust - Quinta (see Louis Marx - Investments) - Stock Sale and Gift (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - 1997 Associates Trust - Quinta (see Louis Marx - Trust Agreement (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Marsh and McLennan Companies, Inc. Settlement - LSR, 2005 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - LSR Friends and Associates Trust - First International Oil Corp., 2002-2008 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Financial - Hills Realty Co. - Stock, 1952 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Financial - Horizons, Inc. - Stock, 1955 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Financial - Inforex, Inc. - Stock, 1971 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, Larry - General, 1991-2007 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - LSR - ITEK Corp., 1957 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Lady Caneel - Leased to Caneel Bay Plat., 1958-1972 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - LSR - McDonnell Aircraft Corporation - Agreements, 1942-1945 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Loan Agreement - New York Trust Company, 1947 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Nuclear Development Corporation of America, 1956 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Nuclear Development Associates, 1954-1956 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Princeton University - Gift, 1982 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Promissory Note - Larry Rockefeller, 1983 February 28 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Promissory Notes, 1982-1986 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - LSR - Puerto Rico Properties, 1954-1975 (Box 119, Folder 11)